http://instrotech.com.au/online-store-policies

[+]
Call us now !
Find us on the map
Send us an email
Home Products Calibrators Indicators Load Cells Soil Probes Tank Level Transmitters Weighing Contact Us Online Shop
Searching
Policies
DELIVERY POLICYRETURNS POLICYPRIVACY POLICY
DELIVERY POLICYWe aim to deliver Products in accordance with your order requirements. Your delivery method options, and the prices for them, are set out in this website or will be notified to you at the time of order. Delivery will be made to the address you nominated unless otherwise agreed in writing.Times and dates for delivery are approximate only and Instrotech is not liable for the consequences of any delay in delivery. Time for delivery shall not be of the essence. Instrotech is not liable for any loss or damage, including indirect, consequential or economic, suffered or incurred by the you or any other party in relation to late delivery.RETURNS POLICYIf for any reason you are not completely satisfied with your purchase from this website, we offer you a 14 day money-back guarantee from the time you received the goods. Please email us atinfo@instrotech.com.auwithin that time period if you are dissatisfied with your purchase so that we may endeavour to resolve any issues.All returned goods MUST be in AS NEW condition including ALL PACKAGING, user DOCUMENTATION and OPERATING MANUALS in order to qualify for a refund.The return freight must be paid by you while the original delivery freight cost is not refundable by Instrotech. You assume any risk of lost, theft or damaged goods during return transit. Instrotech will not be responsible for parcels lost or damaged in transit if you choose not to insure them.This refund policy does not apply to goods which have been used, abused, damaged after delivery, or if any attempt has been made to alter the product or if they have been dropped or broken.PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy addresses personal privacy matters. Its purpose is to explain, in general terms, what sort of personal information we hold and why we hold it, as well as how we collect, use and disclose that information. In this Privacy Policy, where we refer to “you” or “your”, we are referring specifically to natural persons as opposed to other entities such as partnerships, trusts and companies.We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of any personal information individuals are required, or may choose, to give to us. This Privacy Policy represents our position on the management of personal information. It also reflects the requirements of the Privacy Act, Amendments and Regulations, and guidelines issued by the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:  https://www.oaic.gov.auHow do we collect personal information?We will only ask for the personal information that is reasonably required to do business with you. Most information is obtained through online forms at our website. We may also collect personal information via phone or through hardcopy forms.We will not collect non-publicly available personal information about you without your consent and will not buy, rent or otherwise acquire information about you from third parties (such as marketing agencies) without your prior express consent.What information do we collect? How do we use it?The personal information we may collect about you is dependent, to some extent, upon your relationship with us. The following are some examples of the types of personal information that we may collect from individuals:When you sign up for our newsletter, we need only an email address, which we use to send the newsletter you requested.When you submit any suggestion, recommendation, or comment we also ask for your email address although we will not publish your email address without your prior approval. We may use this information to contact you in clarifying any issues you raised.When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and email address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We may also use the information collected to market certain services or products to the contestants. Where we intend to do this, we will advise the contestant of this in the contest’s terms and conditionsWe may also use the information we collect to notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable.An overview of how we use and disclose personal informationSubject to the exceptions set out in the National Privacy Principles (for example, the disclosure of personal information when allowed or required by law), we will only use and/or disclose your personal information for:(a) the primary purpose for which it is collected; or(b) a related purpose, where you would reasonably expect that it be used and/or disclosed without your further consent.Will we send you marketing material in the mail and email and what can you do to stop that?A related purpose for which we collect personal information may be marketing. However, if this is not the case, we are entitled to send marketing material to you provided it gives you a chance to stop or “opt-out” of receiving this material.We will set out in all our standard marketing material details of simple steps that you can take to stop receiving marketing material.We will not charge you any additional cost or in any way disadvantage you if you choose to opt out of receiving marketing material.When do we share information?We will not disclose your personal information to a third party for marketing purposes unless we have obtained your express consent or you have “opted-in”, that is, you have expressly agreed to your personal information being disclosed to a third party.We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.We may release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law or to protect our rights, property or safety of our users, or others.We may disclose your personal information to a likely or actual buyer of the whole or part of the our business, if reasonably necessary for such a sale.Security measures we adopt to protect personal informationWe store personal information in a range of paper-based and electronic forms:(a) Paper Security – Where personal information is stored in physical form, we will use access control measures such as keyed access and security alarms to deter and detect unauthorised access.(b) Computer and Network Security – we adopt a number of security measures to protect information from unauthorised access to its computer systems which include:access control for authorised users such as user passwords and screen saver passwords;limiting access to shared network drives to authorised staff;virus checking;specialised IT support to deal with security risk.(c) Communications Security – Transmission of personal information may involve insecure telecommunications lines. Security of this personal information is enhanced by:checking facsimile numbers before sending personal information, and confirming receipt;passwords required for some internet transmissions;checking identity before giving out any personal information;encryption of data for high risk transmissions.Personal information in our possession may be retained in archival storage. Generally we will destroy personal information after a period of seven (7) years following its collection unless it is required, or may be required, to be kept for a longer period because of the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected.Access to your personal information held by usIf you want access to your personal information held by us, you should put your request in writing and clearly identify the personal information you seek access to. This is important to ensure that the information can be retrieved quickly and cheaply. All requests for access must be addressed to The Privacy Compliance Officer (see contact details below).Depending on the circumstances, we reserve the right to charge you a reasonable administrative fee. For example, our reasonable administrative costs might include:reasonable staff costs in locating and collating the information;reasonable reproduction or photocopying costs; andreasonable costs involved in having someone explain the information to you.In some instances, we may not release the personal information. For example, if the information reveals a formula or the fine details of a commercially sensitive decision-making process, then, in these instances, we may decide to give you an explanation of the commercially-sensitive decision rather than direct access to the information.Alteration of records containing personal informationWe will take reasonable steps to correct any personal information that is inaccurate.Our use of "cookies""Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to track site traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our design, layout and service to users. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use all of the features on our site.Accountability and complaints handlingIf you wish to make a complaint to us about a possible breach of privacy, the complaint should be in writing and clearly set out the nature of the complaint. The complaint should be addressed to The Privacy Compliance Officer (see contact details below).Individuals inquiring about their rights and remedies for breaches of privacy can access detailed information at the website of the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:https://www.oaic.gov.auHow changes to this policy will be notifiedWe may amend the our Privacy Policy from time to time. Amendments to our Privacy Policy may be necessitated by a variety of factors, including, but not limited to, operational and procedural changes and/or the changing legal environment in which we operate.When changes are effected, our Privacy Policy will be updated with the amendments highlighted. The change will be effective on and from the date the amended Privacy Policy is posted on this website.Linked websitesOur website may contain links to other sites not affiliated with us. These sites have their own policies and practices about on-line privacy, and we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these unaffiliated websites.Other Privacy issuesWhenever you post unprotected personal information online in areas accessible to others - for example, chat areas and message boards - that information can be collected and used. Ultimately you are the one who can best control the secrecy of your passwords and account details and you should therefore be careful when you are online.How to contact usInstrotech Australia Pty LtdP O Box 3137Newton SA 5074Australia53a Reynell RoadRostrevor SA 5073Australiatelephone   08 8337 8033telefax        +61 8 8337 8656email           info@instrotech.com.auABN 50 059 798 337
HomeProductsContact UsOnline Shop Copyright © 1999-2020 Instrotech Australia Pty Ltd. All rights reserved.
E&OE. Pricing and Availability may be subject to change without notice.
